isbard36@amail.com

jamieabraham.com

07999 688 021

## Profile

I am a graduate from Bournemouth University with a degree in Games Technology and experience in a variety of programming languages. I am an experienced and effective communicator with a strong eye towards customer satisfaction, thanks to working in retail and customer focused web support.

## Skills

Html and CSS JavaScript (Angular, Vue) jQuery C# (ASP .net) Git, SVN MS-SQL

### Achievements

Awarded a scholarship from Google for the Udactiy Mobile Web Specialist course.

Over 100,000 game plays on web portals for Paramedic, a game I developed as part of a 4 person team in 6 weeks for Edge magazines' "Get into Games" competition.

Developed my skills to achieve a level 2 NVQ in Stock Management at John Lewis and trained as a First Aider.

# Work Experience

### E-mango

#### Full Stack Developer

Feb 2015 - Present

- Develop, test, profile and debug back-end functionality for sites using ASP .NET and C#.
- Design and create responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and iQuerv.
- Support 20 large organisations and 54 town/parish councils to use our CRM and CMS to run and organise their entire business.
- Exercise strong interpersonal skills which are needed to maintain close, professional client relationships.

## John Lewis

#### Stock Management —

Feb 2009 - Jan 2015

- Resolve issues to ensure customer satisfaction and loyalty, showing my commitment to the companies' exceptional customer service ethos.
- Mentor and train over 20 new employees to maximize corporate knowledge retention and take an active role in others development.
- Flexibly fill roles including; team leader, supply chain assistant, service building liaison and customer collections assistant.

### Vision Gear Games

Aug 2012 - Sept 2013

- Engage my entrepreneurial spirit with a group of 3 others to work on passion projects.
- Fill a variety of roles and take part in every part of development, with a focus on gameplay programming and 3d asset creation.
- Organise scrum meetings to evaluate progress to facilitate efficient communication and work.

## Education

# Bournemouth University

2010-2014

Achieved a 2:1 in Games Technology (BSC Hons). Created games in C++ and C#, constructed high and low poly models in 3DSMax and ZBrush, and made textures and sprites in Photshop. Arranged social meetings for the Game Dev Society.

# Itchen College

**2007-2009** 

Achieved 3 A Levels and 2 AS Levels. A Levels in Computing, Physics and Maths, AS Levels in Psychology and Extended Project. The extended project consisted of making a compendium of games in Visual Basic.

# Bitterne Park Secondary School

2002-2007

Attained 12 GCSE's including 3 A\*s at GCSE level including Maths and 8 A's including Physics, IT and Chemistry.